Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Name.
Good evening-
Welcome to
Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?
Are
you ready?
-  Please give
a big round of applause-
-  Good luck. kid.
to our very first
contestant of the night...
Jamal Malik. from our very own...
amchi Mumbai!
Chalo. let's play.
Smile. You'll be fine.
Name.
- Name.
- Jamal... Malik.
You have a name. Good.
Stop crying.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
So. Jamal...
tell me something about yourself.
I work in a call center.
In Juhu.
Good.
A phone basher.
And what type of call center
would that be?
XL 5 mobile phones.
Oh. So you're the one who calls
me up every single day of my
life with special offers. huh?
No. Actually. I'm an assistant.
An assistant phone basher?
And what does a assistant
phone basher do exactly?
I get tea for people and-
Chai wallah.
A chai wallah!
Well. ladies and gentlemen...
Jamal Malik-
...from Mumbai. let's play
Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?
So. has he confessed yet?
Except his name. I could not get
anything out of the runt.
You have been here a whole bloody night.
Srinivas. What have you been doing?
He's a tough guy.
A little electricity will loosen his tongue.
Give him.
Yes. sir.
Okay. So. were you wired up?
Mobile or a pager?
A coughing accomplice
in the audience...
or a microchip under the skin?
Huh?
- The chip is not here.
- Not here?
- No.
- Okay. Leave the chip.
Leave the chip. Leave the chip.
It's hot...
and my wife is giving me hell...
and I've got a desk full of
murderers. rapists...
extortionists. bum bandits and you.
So why don't you save us
both a lot of time...
and tell me how you cheated.
Hmm.
I'm done. sir.
Now. listen.
Hello.
He's unconscious. Juti.
What good is that?
How many times
have I told you. Srinivas?
I'm sorry. sir.
Srinivas. Now we'll have...
Amnesty International here next.
peeing in their pants about human rights.
Sir. I was thinking. um-
- Get him down. tidy him up.
please. for God's sake!
- Sir...
what if he did know the answers?
Professors. doctors. lawyers.
general knowledge wallahs...
never get beyond 16.000 rupees.
He's on 10 million.
What the hell can a...
slumdog possibly know?
The answers.
I knew the answers.
# They can't touch me
We break off. run so fast
they can't even catch me #
# Been that gypsy
Touch me. I show you tricks
with my sticks that quickly #
# Pick up their packs
on my journey #
# Dogs run
They start to follow me
I have my luck #
# Some days they suck
when we live for the buck
we get for the family #
# One day I wanna be a star
so I get to hang in a bar#
# I'll go to Vegas if they pay us
just to forget my scars #
Sorry.
Sorry. Sorry.
Sorry!
# They can't touch me
We break off#
- # Run so fast
they can't even catch me #
# Been that gypsy Touch me #
# I show you tricks
with my sticks that quickly ##
-  Athos!
-  Cried the two musketeers.
-  Musketeers.
-  Athos!
Repeat it.
"You have sent for me. sir."said Athos.
- "You have sent for me. sir."
- Ah.
Huh?
So...
Mr. Malik...
the man who knows all the answers.
Talk.
So. Jamal...
are you ready for the first question
for 1.000 rupees?
Yes.
Not bad money to sit on a chair
and answer a question.
Better than making tea. no?
No. Yes. No.
No? Yes? No?
Is that your final answer?
So. remember. you have
three lifelines.
Ask the audience. fifty-fifty...
phone a friend.
So the first question for 1.000 rupees.
Here we go.
Who was the star in
the 1973 hit film Zanjeer?
Amitabh?
Amitabh Bachchan!
Salim!
Amitabh!
Yea!
Amitabh-
"A."Amitabh Bachchan.
Guess what. You're right.
You just won 1.000 rupees.
You don't have to be a genius.
I knew it was Amitabh Bachchan.
- Hmm?
- Mmm.
Like I said. don't have to be
a genius.
He's the most famous man in India.
A picture of three lions...
is seen in the national
emblem of India.
What is written underneath?
"A." the truth alone triumphs...
"B." lies alone triumph...
"C."fashion alone triumphs...
"D." money alone triumphs?
What do you think. Jamal?
The most famous phrase
of our country.
Would you like to phone a friend?
Ask the audience.
Put the poor man out of his misery.
ladies and gentlemen.
My five-year-old daughter can answer
that question. but you couldn't.
That's strange for
a millionaire genius.
What happened?
Your accomplice nip out for a piss?
The inspector is asking something.
How much is pani puri
at Harish's stall on Chowpatty?
What?
Pani puri. One plate. how much?
- Ten rupees.
- Wrong.
Fifteen since Divali.
Who stole
Constable Vermaas's bicycle...
outside Santa Cruz
station last Thursday?
You know who that was?
Everyone in Juhu knows that.
Even five-year-olds.
Congratulations. Jamal.
You just won 4.000 rupees.
For 16.000 rupees.
Religion.
Interesting.
In depictions of God Rama...
he is famously holding what
in his right hand?
Hey. Jamal.
Jamal-
I wake up every morning wishing I didn't
know the answer to that question.
If it wasn't for Rama and Allah...
I would still have a mother.
A bow and arrow.
Final answer?
Final answer.
Hmm. Ah. Computer-ji.
"D"lock kiya-jaye.
You've just won 16.000 rupees.
Well done. my friend.
Time for a commercial break.
Don't go away now.
You got lucky. huh?
If I were you.
I would take the money and run.
You're not gonna get the next one.
Everybody back in 90. please. Okay?
Can you come and do
the controls. please?
Salim.
Welcome back to Who Wants
to Be a Millionaire?
Our contestant. Jamal Malik.
call center assistant from Mumbai...
is on 16.000 rupees
and has already used one lifeline-
ask the audience.
So. my friend.
you're into serious money.
Yes.
The song "Darshan do Ghanshyam" was
written by which famous Indian poet?
"A."Surdas. "B." Tulsidas...
"C."Mira Bai...
"D."Kabir?
Hello.
It's hot. huh?
Yea!
Arvind.
# Darshan do Ghanshyam #
Salim.
#Darshan do Ghanshyam #
Huh?
Hey.
# Darshan do Ghanshyam #
Salim.
Huh?
Jamal.
Punnoose.
# Darshan do #
#Darshan do Ghanshyam #
# Darshan do Ghanshyam ##
Salim!
Jamal!
Latika.
Latika!
Salim!
Surdas.
Surdas?
Surdas...
apka final answer?
Yes.
Guess what.
You're right!
What happened to the girl?
They blinded her too?
They had other plans.
It took me a long time to find out.
# I fly like paper
get high like planes #
# If you catch me at the border#
- # I got visas in my name
If you come around here #
# I make 'em all day
I get one done
in a second if you wait #
# I fly like paper
get high like planes #
# If you catch me at the border
I've got visas in my name #
# If you come around here
I make 'em all day #
- # I get one done
in a second if you wait #
- Bye! Bye!
# Sometimes I think
sittin' on trains #
# Every stop I get to
I'm clockin' that game #
- # Everyone's a winner
We're makin' our fame #
# Bona fide hustler
I'm makin' my name #
# Sometimes I think sittin' on trains #
- # Every stop I get to
I'm clockin' that game #
- Yea!
# Everyone's a winner
We're makin' our fame #
- # Bona fide hustler
I'm makin' my name #
Hey.
# Pirate skulls and bones #
# Sticks and stones
and weed and bombs #
# Running when we hit 'em #
# Lethal poison
through their system #
# Pirate skulls and bones #
# Sticks and stones
and weed and bombs #
# Running when we hit 'em #
# Lethal poison
through their system #
# No one on the corner
has swagger like us #
# Hit me on my banner
prepaid wireless #
# We pack and deliver
like U.P.S. trucks #
# Already going hell
just pumping that gas #
# No one on the corner
has swagger like us ##
Salim! Salim!
Is this heaven?
You're not dead. Jamal.
What is it?
Some hotel. huh?
The Taj Mahal is considered the finest
example of Mogul architecture.
... who died on June 17. 1631-
during the birth
of their 14th child.
The Taj Mahal was completed around. uh.
1648. using a labor force of 20.000 workers-
In 1980 it became a UNESCO
World Heritage Site and was cited as the-
If you would like to follow me...
I will show you 99 names of Allah
on Mumtaz's tomb.
Please take off your shoes.
Please. Please.
What time is the next tour?
We are on a very tight
schedule. you see.
Have to see the Red Fort
this afternoon.
- No. I-
- Please. would it be possible...
to show us around now?
Obviously we understand
that it costs more for just the two of us.
But of course. madam.
Please follow me.
The Taj Mahal was built
by Emperor Khurram...
for his wife Mumtaz.
Was the maximum beautiful
woman in the world.
So. when she died. the emperor decided
to build this...
five-star hotel...
for everyone
who'd like to visit her too.
But he died in 1587...
before any of the rooms
were built or any of the lifts.
But the swimming pool.
as you can see...
was completed on schedule.
in top-class fashion.
There's nothing of this
in the guidebook.
The guidebook was written by a bunch of
lazy. good-for-nothing Indian beggars.
Oh.
And this. lady and gentleman.
is the burial place of Mumtaz.
How did she die?
- A road traffic accident.
- Really?
Maximum pileup.
I thought she died in childbirth.
Exactly. sir. She was on the way
to hospital when it happened.
Ready?
Don't move an inch.
Smile.
Unbreakable Thailand wood.
You take. Shoes!
American brands! Shoes!
- # All I wanna do
And a-#
-
# Then take your money
'Cause all I wanna do #
# And a-
Then take your money #
# All I wanna do
And a-#
# Then take your money #
# And a-#
- # All I wanna do #
- Smile!
# And a-
And take your money #
# All I wanna do
And a-#
# Then take your money #
This. Mr. David. is the biggest dhobi ghat
in the whole of India.
That's amazing.
Come on.
Take a real good look at this.
They say that every man
in Uttar Pradesh...
is wearing a kurta that has been
at least washed once out here.
Formula One! Formula One!
Pit stop ka speed!
Schumacher ka style!
The-The cows. the-the buffaloes.
What are those over there?
Oh. shit.
What the hell happened here?
Okay-
Okay! Okay!
Cool it! Cool it. will ya? Jesus.
- You got insurance. don't ya?
Are you okay?
- You wanted to see a bit
of real India. here it is.
- All right!
- Well. here is a bit of
the real America. son.
Oh. Yes. yes. Jesus.
Here.
#Eurydice #
# Eurydice #
On an American $ 100 bill...
there is a portrait
of which American statesman?
"A." George Washington...
"B." Franklin Roosevelt...
"C." Benjamin Franklin...
"D." Abraham Lincoln?
Pay or play. Jamal?
You decide.
Oh. God. He's looking at the camera.
He hasn't got a clue.
This is gonna be a walk-away.
Stand by.
No. He's gonna play with him first.
Jamal.
Get a lot of $100 bills
in your line of work?
The minimum tip for my services.
Oh.
Now I know why my cell phone
bills are so high.
They tip the chai wallah
with $100 bills.
It's "C."
Benjamin Franklin.
- You're gonna play. huh?
- I think I just have. haven't I?
You certainly have.
"C."right? Right?
Who's on the thousand-rupee note?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Gandhi-ji.
Oh. I've heard of him.
Don't get clever...
or I'll get the electricity
out again.
Look.
They didn't ask me that question.
I don't know why.
Ask them.
It's funny. You don't seem
that interested in money.
As a matter of fact. you have...
one million rupees!
Explain the $100 bill.
Bombay had turned into Mumbai.
Why can't you understand?
I'm sick of this now.
Two chicken burgers. two fries.
one mango lassi. one Coke.
One mineral water.
Shimla.
I'm going to Chowpatty. okay?
Wanna come?
For God's sake.
You've got some disease.
You forced me back
to this shithole...
we leave our friends. a good life.
loads of money... for this?
- We came back to find her.
- You did.
I don't give a shit about her.
Plenty of pussy in Bombay for Salim.
Oh. yes. sir.
You should come back to the cages
on Saturday night...
instead of go searching
for your lost love.
I'm going to Chowpatty.
"I'm going to Chowpatty."
There are 19 million people
in this city. Jamal.
Forget about her.
She's history.
Dollars?
100.
Benjamin Franklin.
I'm sorry. Arvind.
Thanks.
Oh. Sorry.
Cherry?
So. is it her or not?
She's sexy. man.
Latika!
- Who is this?
- Jamal?
- I'll get the bag.
- Who are you? What do you want?
- Quick!
- You stupid boys.
- Come on. Pack it in.
- What are you doing?
- How did you find me?
- Later. Later.
No. not everything.
Get out. if you can.
-  Take the cash. Take the cash.
-  Come on. We gotta go.
Let's go. Let's go. Shit.
Look who we have here.
Hello again...
Jamal...
Salim.
Never forget a face.
Hey. Punnoose?
Especially one that I own.
You really thought you could just walk in
and take my prize away?
Latika. come.
Have you any idea
how much this little virgin is worth?
- Please continue. Master-ji.
- Okay. sir.
- Get them out of here.
- No!
Move!
Get over there.
Let's not be foolish. Salim.
Heavy. isn't it?
Give it to me.
Huh?
On your knees. Down!
Both of you. down!
Money!
You can have money.
Here.
Look.
Take it. Go.
Disappear with your... friend.
and we'll forget all about this. Okay?
Maman never forgets.
Isn't that right?
Oh. Maman can
make an exception. huh?
I can't take that risk.
Maman. Sorry.
Let's go!
Stay!
Jamal!
Jamal.
Let's go! Let's go!
Who invented the revolver?
Samuel Colt.
Final answer?
Final answer.
Jamal Malik...
you're on a dream run.
My heart says you're gonna win more.
Computer-ji...
"A"lock kiya-jaye.
I was right.
The chai wallah has done it again.
Incredible!
- Service!
- Reception!
Oh!
- Found something.
-  Stay there. Look away.
I know if you're looking.
No. I'm not.
Is Salim still there?
Where's Salim?
Don't know.
You're a sweet boy. Jamal.
I'm looking for Javed.
He's not looking for you.
I killed Maman.
And I'll kill you too.
Easy.
Did you really kill him?
Good.
My enemy's enemy is a friend.
Come here. my friend.
Mm. I've been looking
for someone like you.
You came back for me.
Of course.
I thought you'd forgotten.
I never forgot.
Not for one moment.
I knew I'd find you in the end.
It's our destiny.
Destiny.
Hey.
Come.
No. Brother.
You've had a lot to drink.
I am the elder. I am the boss.
For once you do as I say.
Now get out.
Come on.
I saved your life. didn't I?
Salim. please-
I'll kill you!
Kill you!
I am number one now.
Salim!
Salim. open it!
Shut up!
The man with the Colt.45
says shut up!
Go now. or Gunmaster G-9 will
shoot you right between the eyes.
Don't think he won't.
I'm giving you five seconds.
One...
two-
Go. Jamal.
Go.
So. did you see them again?
I wouldn't be here if I had.
Was she pretty?
I guess not.
The most beautiful
woman in the world.
He means "the bitch of the slums."
Hey. Hey!
Hey. no-
Well. well.
The slumdog barks.
Money and women-
the reasons to make
most mistakes in life.
Correct.
Looks like you're
mixed up with both.
Srinivas.
You need the exercise.
Go and get me something to eat.
Yes. sir.
And chai.
Phaode!
Idiot. Srinivas.
You puzzle me. slumdog-
admitting murder to avoid
the charge of fraud...
is not exactly clever thinking.
Now. why would you do that?
Hmm?
When somebody asks me a question...
I tell them the answer.
Hmm.
So. how did you manage
to get on the show?
Okay. everyone. Listen up.
It's been a big week for U.K.
Kat is back.
But she was already back.
Bardi. Jamal?
Oh. well. she did come back.
Then she went away...
when Alfie split up with her.
and now she's back again.
But it looks as if Alfie
still fancies Mo after all.
Thank you. Jamal.
Bardi. keep up.
The chai wallah knows more than you.
Anyway. there's also
the festival in Edinburgh.
Anybody knows Edinburgh?
Edinburgh?
Ah. kilts. castles.
uh. haggis. uh. Ben Nevis.
Good. Yes?
Inspector Taggart. whiskey. Sean Connery.
Good. And lochs-
their word for lakes.
No filming.
Jamal. come here.
I'm on Millionaire duty today.
- Dave-
- Please. Just for five minutes.
I can't.
Sit here.
If the team leader comes...
- just pretend you are on a call
doing an upgrade for-
- Friends and Family. I know.
- Yah.
- Two minutes.
Ah.
Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?
Dial this number now.
Answer this question.
What does "A.T.M."-
Hello? Hello? Hello?
I would like to be a contestant
on Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?
-  Hello? I want to be on-
- Uh-
Bloody bastard.
I never get it!
You have to dial
when Prem says "if."
- That's when they open the lines.
- How the hell do you know that?
That's what Anjum in technical says.
He put the system in.
Hello? Hello?
Have I been transferred again.
for God's sake?
Hello? Good God.
will somebody talk to me?
Uh. hello...
Mrs. Mackintosh
from..."King-uss-ie."
It's Kingussie. love.
Pronounced "Kingussie."
So where are you from?
Abroad. I bet.
Uh. just down the road
from your house. Mrs. Mackintosh.
Uh. next to the loch.
Och aye?
Which loch?
Loch-
Loch- Big... Loch Ben.
Loch Big Ben. Next door
to Sean Connery's flat.
I'd like to speak to your supervisor. son.
-  Yes?
- Salim?
Who is this?
Do you know what time is this?
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Who is this?
I'm calling from
XL 5 Communications. sir.
As a valued customer.
we are offering you a free upgrade...
with our Friends and-
Family-
Jamal?
I-Is that you. Brother?
Where are you?
I thought you were dead or something.
Listen. We had to go. Jamal.
Maman's guys- they were
searching the hotel.
Jamal? Say something. please!
Hello. Salim.
Cambridge Circus is not in Cambridge.
Dare I ask why?
Too obvious.
There's definitely
an Oxford Circus in London.
And there's a rowing race between Oxford
and Cambridge. so there's probably...
a Cambridge Circus too. no?
I'll go for "D." London.
Computer-ji. "D"lock kiya-jaye.
Jamal Malik...
you're absolutely right!
It's getting hot in here.
- Are you nervous?
- What?
Am I nervous?
It's you who's in
the hot seat. my friend.
Oh. yes.
Sorry.
Bloody hell. he's got Prem on the run.
- Finally.
- A few hours ago...
you were giving chai
for the phone wallahs.
And now you're richer
than they will ever be.
What a player.
Ladies and gentlemen. what a player!
Jamal?
God is good. bhai.
God is good.
Maman's guys were after us.
We just had to skip.
- Liar.
- Left a message for you at work.
- Waited weeks for you at Nagpur.
- There was no message.
Bhai. I definitely left a message.
There was no message. There was
no message! There was no message!
I will never forgive you.
I know.
That used to be our slum.
Can you believe that. huh?
We used to live right there. man.
Now it's all business.
India is at the center
of the world hub. bhai.
And I-
I am at the center...
of the center.
This is all Javed-bhai's.
- Javed Khan?
- Sorry.
The gangster from our slum?
You work for him?
Come on. Who else do you think would
save us from Maman's guys. huh?
What do you do for him?
Anything he asks.
He's coming.
You need to go now.
- Take my card.
- What for?
You think I'm gonna let you
out of my sights again. huh?
You stay with me now.
younger brother.
Now go- my place.
Salim. where is Latika?
Still?
She's gone. Brother.
Long gone. Now go.
Go to my place.
- # Hey #
- Hello?
Okay. I'll be right there.
# Hey #
# Hey ##
I'm the new cook from the agency.
A thousand apologies.
I am so late for the memsahib.
Just a minute.
Excuse me.
There's nothing about any cook.
There is a dishwasher being delivered.
Do you know anything about that?
I am your dishwasher.
Jamal.
Look at you.
I found you.
Your face.
You've hurt your eye.
Why are you here?
To see you.
Well. you see me.
Now what?
"C."Eden's Bridge...
or "D."Apple's Bridge.
Why does everyone love this program?
It's a chance to escape. isn't it?
Walk into another life.
Oh. God.
Javed will kill you.
Just- Here.
Javed? You're with him?
First you order a dishwasher.
Now you want this fucking cook. huh?
- I just thought-
- Shut up!
The cricket is on.
And why do you watch this shit TV?
As it is I am a millionaire.
Come on. I'm hungry.
Make me a sandwich.
I want to bet five lakh rupees
he'll make a century.
Ah! Make it seven then.
Mm. Yeah.
Come away with me.
Away where?
And live on what?
Love.
Come away with me... now.
Mm!
Salim will help us.
Salim?
You still believe in Salim?
Jamal. I'll be gone soon anyway.
We're getting out of Bombay.
Where?
- Do you think he'd tell me?
-  No.
Not the second- No!
No! No!
And could that be
a hundred for Tendulkar?
To the third umpire. Billy Bowden.
Takes the fielder on.
In the deep.
That's a good throw.
Flat.
He looks confident.
Yeah. I wouldn't be.
Boucher seems very. very confident.
What is this shit?
Get out.
Get out!
Now go... before he kills us both.
- You want to do something for me?
- Anything.
- Then forget me.
- What? No.
I'll wait...
at the V.T. station 5:00 every day
until you come.
I love you.
So what?
It's too late. Jamal.
Now go.
So. Jamal. which cricketer
has scored...
the most first class
centuries in history?
"A." Sachin Tendulkar...
"B." Ricky Ponting...
"C." Michael Slater...
or "D."Jack Hobbs?
But remember. if you answer wrong...
you lose everything-
just like this.
So do you want to do this?
That's the way. Jamal!
Dreams of so many...
on the floor.
Latika. Latika!
Latika!
Latika! Latika!
Jamal!
Jamal! Jamal!
Latika!
Latika! Latika!
Time for a commercial break.
ladies and gentlemen.
I know. I know.
I can't stand the tension either.
We'll be right back.
Guy from the slums...
becomes a millionaire overnight.
Do you know who's the only
other person who's done that?
Me.
I know what it feels like.
I know what you've been through.
I'm not going to become a millionaire.
I don't know the answer.
You've said that before. yeah.
No. Really.
This time I don't.
Come on. You can't take
the money and run now.
You're on the edge of history. kid.
I don't see what else I can do.
Maybe it's written. my friend.
I don't know.
I just get some kind of karmic feeling
you're going to win this.
Trust me. Jamal.
You're going to win.
Stand by. everyone.
We're on live in 30.
Get him back
on the floor. yeah. Prem is waiting.
Yeah. he's coming. He's coming.
I'm just getting him.
Go first.
Twenty seconds.
Do the right thing. and in approximately
three minutes. you'll be as famous as me.
Ten seconds.
And as rich as me.
Almost.
Five seconds. Four. three-
From rags to raja.
It's your destiny.
We are on!
Applause and music. please!
Jib move out.
Cut to two.
Welcome back to
Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?
In the chair tonight is Jamal Malik.
-  Yeah!
- As if you don't know.
For 10 million rupees-
The question once again:
Which cricketer has scored
the most first class centuries in history?
- I know it isn't Sachin Tendulkar.
- That's a start.
So it could be Ricky Ponting...
Jack Hobbs or Michael Slater.
I'll use a lifeline- fifty-fifty.
Okay. Computer. take away
two wrong answers. please.
Well. you were right
about Sachin Tendulkar.
That leaves you a fifty-fifty choice. Jamal.
"B." Ricky Ponting...
or "D."Jack Hobbs?
What do you think?
Decision time.
For 10 million rupees.
"B." Ricky Ponting...
or "D."Jack Hobbs?
"D."
Not "B"?
"B."Ricky Ponting...
the Australian great cricketer?
"D."Jack Hobbs.
You know?
So it could be "B." Ricky Ponting.
Or "D."Jack Hobbs.
Final answer- "D."
Computer-ji. "D."
"D"lock kiya-jaye.
Computer-ji. "D"lock kiya-jaye.
With...
197 first class centuries.
the answer is...
"D."Jack Hobbs!
Jamal Malik-
millionaire!
I cannot believe my eyes.
ladies and gentlemen!
This needs a dance. man!
Come on! Come on!
Well done. Well done.
So. are you ready...
for the final question?
For 20 million rupees.
No.
But maybe it's written. no?
Maybe.
Okay. the final question
on Who Wants to Be a-
What a show. ladies and gentlemen.
What a show!
Join us tomorrow night to see...
if Jamal Malik has made
the biggest mistake of his life...
or just won the biggest prize
in the history of Indian television.
- This way.
- Yeah. Let's just-
Come. Jamal.
Great show.
See you tomorrow. okay?
Be on time.
- Yeah.
- Bye.
Careful.
What's going on?
- He's a cheat.
- How do you know he's cheating?
Bloody village boy.
I fed him the wrong answer.
and that little shit got it right.
You gave him an answer?
Not exactly.
But how does it matter?
It's- It's my show.
It's my fucking show!
It is bizarrely plausible.
- And yet-
- Because I'm a slumdog. a chai wallah...
- I'm a liar. right?
- Most of you are.
But you are not a liar. Mr. Malik.
That's for sure.
You're too truthful.
We're done.
I don't know where
they've taken her.
Latika.
I went on the show...
because I thought she'd be watching.
Did Jamal Malik...
an uneducated 18-year-old boy
from the slums of Mumbai...
win one crore by fair means
or foul play?
In the crowd around me.
there is an even bigger question.
Will he be back tonight to play for another
20 million rupees?
Jamal Malik-
Hey. you. come here. Give me a kiss.
- Come here.
-  You want it?
Yeah. I want it. Come on. girls!
And if there wasn't
enough drama in a contestant...
reaching the final question.
Jamal Malik...
was last night arrested...
- on suspicion of fraud.
-  That guy-
He will never give up.
Never.
Crazy chutiye.
- Go.
- But-
Just drive.
There won't be another chance.
He will kill you.
I'll take care of him.
Salim.
I can't.
You have to.
For God's sake. hold on to this.
And for what I've done.
please forgive me.
Have a good life.
You're back on the show.
Come on!
Come on.
The nation is gripped
with Millionaire fever tonight...
as Jamal Malik. an uneducated young man
from the Juhu slum in Mumbai...
won a staggering
10 million rupees...
on the television show
Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?
An estimated 90 million people
will tune in tonight...
to see if he can go one stage
further and win...
an unthinkable 20 million rupees.
Come on!
Where is everyone?
Get back in here.
Get back to work.
Now.
Chai wallah?
Welcome back
to Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?
I can safely say that tonight...
is the biggest night
of both our lives.
Jamal Malik. the call center
worker from Mumbai...
has already won a cool 10 million.
He can walk away
with that in his pocket...
or make the biggest gamble
in television history...
and go for the final question...
and a staggering 20 million rupees.
Are you ready for that question?
- Yes.
- Jamal!
Big reader. are you. Jamal?
I can read.
Lucky.
In Alexander Dumas's book...
The Three Musketeers...
two of the musketeers are
called Athos and Porthos.
What was the name
of the third musketeer?
"A."Aramis.
"B."Cardinal Richelieu...
"C." D'Artagnan...
or "D." Planchet?
Athos!
Final question for 20 million rupees.
and he's smiling.
I guess you know the answer.
Do you believe it? I don't.
You don't?
So you take the 10 million and walk?
No.
I'll play.
Let me remind you. Jamal.
If you get the answer wrong...
you lose everything.
Ten million rupees. Jamal.
It's a fortune.
I'd like to phone a friend.
We're going to the wire.
The final lifeline.
Here we go.
It's ringing.
Who is it?
It's my brother's number. but-
The kind of brother who'd go for a walk...
on a 20 million rupee question?
It's the only number I know.
You are on your own. Jamal.
Hello?
Hello. Jamal?
I'm guessing
that isn't your brother.
This is?
My name is Latika.
Okay. Latika. You want to hear
the question one more time?
And let's be clear about this.
Twenty million rupees ride on your answer.
You have 30 seconds.
- Latika!
- Jamal...
- please read out the question...
- Salim!
to Latika now.
Is that really you?
-  Yes.
- The question. Jamal. The question.
In Alexander Dumas's book.
The Three Musketeers...
two of the musketeers are
called Athos and Porthos.
What was the name
of the third musketeer?
Was it "A."Aramis.
"B."Cardinal Richelieu...
"C." D'Artagnan. "D." Planchet?
- Fifteen seconds.
- Where are you?
I'm safe.
Ten seconds.
Latika. what do you think?
I don't know.
I've never known.
Jamal-
You really are
on your own now. Jamal.
Your final answer
for 20 million rupees.
"A."
"A." because?
Just... because.
Hey. Salim!
Final answer?
Yes.
Final answer- "A." Aramis.
Computer-ji.
"A"lock kiya-jaye.
Salim!
Jamal Malik.
Call center assistant from Mumbai.
Chai wallah.
For two crore-
twenty million rupees.
You were asked who the third
musketeer was-
in the novel by Alexander Dumas.
You answered "A"...
Aramis...
which is...
I have to tell you...
the right answer!
Jamal Malik!
Double crorepati!
God is great.
What a night!
Ladies and gentlemen...
we are present here...
to create... history!
Well done!
Yea!
I knew you'd be watching.
I thought we'd meet again
only in death.
This is our destiny.
Kiss me.
# Hey #
# Hey ##
#They can't touch me #
# We break off. run so fast
they can't even catch me #
# Been that gypsy
Touch me #
# I show you tricks
with my sticks that quickly #
# One day I wanna be a star#
# So I get to hang in a bar#
# I'll go to Vegas
if they pay us #
# Just to forget my scars ##
Subtitles by LeapinLar
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm